<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on NZ Louis&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.nzlouis.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on NZ Louis&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.nzlouis.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microservices Architecture Empowering Online Banking Services: Secure, Efficient, and Scalable</title>
      <link>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/28/microservices-architecture-empowering-online-banking-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/28/microservices-architecture-empowering-online-banking-services/</guid>
      <description>Microservices Architecture Empowering Online Banking Services: Secure, Efficient, and Scalable 1. What is Online Banking Service? Online banking service is a digital extension of banking operations, allowing customers to perform various banking activities through internet channels (web or mobile applications). Typical functionalities include account management, fund transfers, bill payments, loan applications, investment management, and more. Many banks are increasingly providing services through online channels to better meet customer demands.&#xA;2. Differences Between Online Banking Systems and Other Software Systems 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand: A Paradise for Children</title>
      <link>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/20/new_zealand_paradise_for_children/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/20/new_zealand_paradise_for_children/</guid>
      <description>New Zealand, a picturesque nation known for its stunning natural landscapes, high-quality living standards, and comprehensive social welfare, is widely regarded as a paradise for children.&#xA;Overview New Zealand, a safe and stable country with a low crime rate and excellent public safety, consistently achieves high rankings in international indices such as the 2023 United Nations Human Development Index and Global Peace Index. With a crime rate of only 1,900 per 100,000 people, as per the data from Statistics New Zealand, it provides a secure and healthy environment for children to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will AI Completely Replace Human Developers?</title>
      <link>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/10/will-ai-replace-human-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/10/will-ai-replace-human-developers/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Will AI code robots steal programmers&amp;rsquo; jobs? Not so fast. This article proposes a novel &amp;ldquo;Five Levels of AI-ization&amp;rdquo; framework inspired by self-driving cars, predicting AI&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on software development. Expect AI to become a powerful partner, automating routine tasks and boosting efficiency, not replacing human creativity and strategic thinking. Dive in to explore the future of AI and developers, working together to build the next generation of software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vim Tips</title>
      <link>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/05/vim-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.nzlouis.com/2024/01/05/vim-tips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;vim-graphical-cheat-sheet&#34;&gt;vim graphical cheat sheet&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;//img/2018-02-09-vim-tips/vi-vim-cheat-sheet.svg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
